module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who wrote the 1986 song "The Final Countdown"?', 
    a: 'Def Leppard',
    b: 'Scorpions',
    c: 'Journey',
    d: 'Europe',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'In what year did American women win the right to vote?', 
    a: '1920',
    b: '1933',
    c: '1875',
    d: '1917',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of animal is the largest primate in the world?', 
    a: 'Tarsier',
    b: 'Human',
    c: 'Gorilla',
    d: 'Orangutan',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who served as Microsoft\'s CEO after Bill Gates?', 
    a: 'Larry Page',
    b: 'Satya Nadella',
    c: 'Sergey Brin',
    d: 'Steve Ballmer',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which Egyptian goddess is pictured as a cat or as a woman with the head of a cat?',
    a: 'Thoth',
    b: 'Bastet',
    c: 'Nekhbet',
    d: 'Isis',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The fictional character "Captain Ahab" appears in which novel?', 
    a: 'Moby Dick',
    b: 'Treasure Island',
    c: 'Robinson Crusoe',
    d: 'Gulliver\'s Travels',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which film hero has a girlfriend named "Marion Ravenwood"?', 
    a: 'James Bond',
    b: 'Indiana Jones',
    c: 'Batman',
    d: 'Rocky Balboa',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What instrument was played by the famous jazz musician "Louis Armstrong"?', 
    a: 'Trumpet',
    b: 'Piano',
    c: 'Saxophone',
    d: 'Drums',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a Girl Scout cookie?', 
    a: 'Samoas',
    b: 'Bredelas',
    c: 'Thin Mints',
    d: 'Do-si-dos',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'The characters of Rosencrantz and Guildenstern appear in which Shakespeare play?', 
    a: 'Hamlet',
    b: 'Othello',
    c: 'Romeon and Juliet',
    d: 'Macbeth',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
